<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Motivation>
  <Quotes>
    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>One moment on the lips, a lifetime on the hips.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>Before you eat it, think do you really need it?</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>Eat to live, not live to eat.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>This food is evil, it wants to STOP you from REACHING YOUR GOALS.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>Don't Let your cravings control your FUTURE.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>Junk food's are engineered to addict you to chemical ingredients.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>It doesn't matter how hard you work in the gym if you don't control what you put on your plate.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>Working out is the EASY part, EATING HEALTHY is the HARD part.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>
        It's HARD to say NO to junk food right? &#13;If you eat that you will have to EXERCISE for THREE MORE HOURS to burn off the additional calories.&#13;So which is HARDER?
      </content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>When You feel like eating junk food just imagine about how you will feel after eating it.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>Eat it if you want to kill HOURS of HARD WORK in the gym for a PLEASURE that will only last for few SECONDS.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>Don't Give Up What You Want Most, For What You Want Now.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>When you can't control your cravings go drink 2 galss of water and then ask yourself do you really need this?</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="junk">
      <content>Nothing tastes as good as being healthy feels.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>It's not about how good you are, it's about how good you want to be.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>Don't let life change your goals because acheiving the goals can change your life.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>The distance between who you are and who you want to be are seperated by your actions.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>You have to do what others don't to achieve what others won't.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>Successfull people do daily what other do occasionally.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>You don't get what you want &#13; you get what you work for.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>The secret of getting ahead is getting started.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>Motivation is what gets you started. Habit is what keeps you going.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>Being Defeated is a TEMPORARY condition, giving up is what makes it PERMANTENT</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>It is a shame for a man to grow old without seeing the STRENGTH and BEAUTY of which his body is capable.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>Squat beacuse somewhere there is a girl warming up with your max.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>If you don't live for something you'll die for nothing.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>First they ask you why you do it &#13; then they ask you how you did it.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>You are not born as a champion. You become a champion.</content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="notmotivated" >
      <content>Don't give up begining is always the hardest.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>
        NO PAIN NO GAIN
        So suffer the PAIN and enjoy the GAIN
      </content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>The PAIN of today id the VICTORY of tommorow</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>Is it hard? do you feel the pain and dizziness? Good its WORKING</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>It's not going to be EASY, But it's going to be WORTH IT</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>
        Of Course it's HARD, it's SUPPOSED to be HARD. If it's EASY everyone would do it.
        HARD is what makes it GREAT
      </content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>
        PAIN is WEAKNESS leaving the body.
        Suffer the PAIN or stay WEAK.
      </content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>
        Pain is the little voice in your head that tries to hold you back beacuse it knows IF YOU CONTINUE, YOU WILL CHANGE
        Don't Let it stop you from BEING WHO YOU CAN BE!
      </content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>
        Think TRAINING'S HARD?
        try LOSING.
      </content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>
        There is a secret diet pill for success.
        It's called "WORK YOUR BUTT OFF EVERYDAY!"
      </content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>Strong people are the one who FEEL, UNDERSTAND and ACCEPT PAIN.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>PAIN is TEMPORARY, but QUITING makes it PERMANENT! </content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>
        You have two choices.
        Suffer the pain of WORKOUT or suffer the pain of REGRET!
      </content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>Workout might be PAINFUL or TOUGH, but it's not as PAINFUL or TOUGH as skipping it.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>There are no shortcuts to any place worth going.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>If you TRAIN hard you'll not only be hard, you'll be hard to BEAT.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>If it doesn't CHALLENGE you, It doesn't CHANGE YOU!</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="harder" >
      <content>Better SORE than SORRY. </content>
    </Quote>

    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>ROME wasn't built in ONE DAY</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>Losing weight is not a race, be patient.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>No matter how SLOW you go you are LAPPING everyone on the couch.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>The progress will be SLOW but it's worth it.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>When you feel like giving up PUSH HARDER.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>In order to get results from exercise, you have to regularly push yourself beyond your fitness comfort zone</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>Did you stop eating junk? By eating JUNK food you are UNDOING all the PROGRESS that you made at the gym.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>Be patient. Remember that you're creating a lifestyle change that you can sustain for the rest of your life</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>Are you sleeping properly? SLEEP is equally important as WORKOUT! Remember muscles are TEARED in the GYM, FED in the KITCHEN and BUILT in the BED.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>SLOW progress is BETTER than NO progress.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>Its not all about workout, but what you do the rest of the day matters, too. Sitting whole day will UNDO all your hardwork at the gym! It will store fat around your waist!</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>I may not be there yet but i'm closer than I was yesterday</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>You can't change from day to day. But year after year you can.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>Don't abandon your dream just because it demands the time.</content>
    </Quote>
    <Quote  Category ="noresult" >
      <content>Good things come to those who wait.</content>
    </Quote>




  </Quotes>
</Motivation>